BRYANT MACMAHON

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Full Stack Software Engineer with 2 years of Programming experience and 5 years of experience in Business Management. Problem solving enthusiast and strong communicator with fervor to bring skills, talents and energy to a development team solving modern, innovative and challenging software issues.

SKILLS

Coding Languages

Javascript, Typescript, Python, CSS, HTML, SQL

Frameworks/Technologies

React, Tailwind, Flask, Node.js, Git Expres s.js, jQuery, Jest, Jasmine, Bootstrap, REST A PIs, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Chrome Devtoo ls, Bash/Shell, Visual Studio, Markdown, Notion

Key Strengths

Googling, Test Driven Development, Agile

EDUCATION

Springboard Software Engineering Career Track | March 2021 - December 2021

- Mastering skills in front-end web development, back-end web development, databases, data structures and algorithms.
- Weekly 1 on 1 meetings with a senior level, industry expert.
- 800+ hours of course material
- 400+ hours of coding editor time

Indiana University Bloomington - Bachelor of Science: Mangement - School of Public and Environmental Affairs | September 2011 - June 2013

- Treasurer Inter-fraternity Council
- Social Chair Theta Chi Fraternity

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Secured Investment Corp | Feb 2022 - Present

- Currently building a full stack progressive web app that allows users to leverage real estate methods to purchase assets.
- Used UI/UX strategies to design a modern and enticing front end for customers.
- Created database architecture to track and extract vital data for business intelligence usage.
- Adhered to agile methodologies and used CI/CD to meet both customer and business needs.
- <u>Stack</u>: React, Typescript, Javascript, Tailwind, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Figma, SQL, PHP, Digital Ocean

Full Stack Developer

Bird Digital | December 2020 - Feb 2021

- Designed and deployed static websites for customers with various front end needs.
- Built Voice, Messaging and Fax Interactive Relay systems with Node.js.
- Wire-framed projects in Figma and converted to React.
- · Maintained and tested React code.
- <u>Stack</u>: React, TypeScript, Node, Gatsby, Figma, Shopify, Google Cloud, SignalWire, Stripe, MindBody

CONTACT

Phone: 208.908.3163

Email: bryantmac@gmail.com

Portfolio: zataara.xyz Location: Portland, OR

Linked In: linkedin.com/in/bryantmac

Github: github.com/zataara